g-shock.com 2016-11-19

# Casio G-Shock Website Privacy Information | Casio - G-Shock

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this privacy statement notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

This web site may contain links to other organizations’ web sites, including potential links to sites for individual Casio dealers/distributors. Casio is not >responsible for the privacy policy or practices or the content of such web sites. 

By visiting this web site you accept the policies and practices described in this Privacy Statement. Casio reserves the right to make changes to this notice by posting such changes on this web site. Changes are effective immediately upon posting unless a different effective date is stated. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Casio website.

**The Information We Collect and How We Use It**

Required information. There are pages on this site where we request specific information about you, in order to register you for membership on the site, process your orders, fulfill your requests for information, and to communicate with you about past orders and to keep your knowledge about our products and services current. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * Name 
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Credit/Debit Card Information
  * Optional Demographic Information
  * Age Group
  * Earning Bracket
  * Gender
  * Your preference regarding future receipt of product information e-mail messages from Casio.

On some pages, we may request that you submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

  * Name
  * Address
  * Phone Number 

Whenever we require information from you, it is our policy to collect and save such information so that we do not need to ask you for it repeatedly. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of the features in this web site.

**Registration**

You can register on our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you agree to this on the registration form. When you register for membership on the site, we provide you with the opportunity to “opt out” of receiving any catalog, product, service or other informational emails from Casio. If you choose to “opt out”, we will only use your return email addresses to answer the email we receive and to provide necessary status information regarding your orders or your membership. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

**Orders**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

**Optional Information supplied voluntarily**. 

From time to time, we may invite you to participate in voluntary surveys or otherwise supply additional certain optional information. Responding to these requests is completely voluntary and is your choice. We collect and analyze information voluntarily supplied via surveys or otherwise in order to track and improve service to our customers and potential customers, for internal marketing purposes, and for any additional purposes indicated in the request for information.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. We also use this demographic information in designing and evaluating new products that Casio manufactures.

Automatic collection of information. Like many web sites, our site may periodically utilize a technology called “cookies.” A cookie is a small data file that a web server can deliver to your browser, which is then stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are designed to permit us to provide better or more personalized service when you are visiting our site, and can also identify web sites visited between visits to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, providing you with as much control as you wish as to the decision to accept/reject the cookie, and deletion of the cookie upon leaving our web site. Refer to your browser's Help information for details on setting cookie notification services. We may also track the Internet domains from which people contact us, and from time-to-time may gather information concerning the “referring” domain that a person visited prior to our site, and the “destination” domain a person visits after leaving our site. Information automatically collected is used to identify and analyze the trends and statistics of visits to our web site and to make our web site more responsive to the needs and interests of our customers.

**Disclosure of Information**

Information about our customers is important to our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. There may be times when we will need to disclose your information to our providers, contractors or distributors for the purpose of fulfilling an order for products and services requested by you, or otherwise processing transactions and related information. Before doing so, we will require the organizations receiving such information to commit to the same level of protection for your information as is provided in this Privacy Notice. We will not knowingly distribute your name, address or other information you provide outside of the Casio family of subsidiaries and affiliates, or publicize the fact that you submitted information to us, unless we ask your permission or notify you beforehand, or we are required to do so by law or government order. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to those described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Choice**   
By providing personal and business information and accepting any cookies provided by Casio, you consent to our collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Notice. If you do not agree to the provisions of this Privacy Notice, you can refuse to register, refuse to accept cookies, or refuse to volunteer optional information. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security  
**  
It is not possible for web sites to achieve perfect security. We do, however, take commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial precautions using widely accepted methods to safeguard the security of your information against inadvertent disclosure to unauthorized persons. Security controls may include standard 128-bit SSL (Secure Socket Layers) to protect the security of information transmitted directly through this website. As is generally the case, this protection does not extend to Internet e-mail messages sent outside this website directly to and from individual e-mail addresses.

**Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**Access to your information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintained by Casio through your “My Account” page (click here for more information regarding your account). We use this method to allow you, the Casio member, to correct, amend or delete any inaccurate entries, and to better maintain and safeguard your information. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 800-962-2746 or send us an email at [memberservices@casio.com](mailto:memberservices@casio.com).
